The matter has been connected with Ashwatthama
till last week, welcome to the entire front, I hope
in Gurgaon, the water has
melted a lot and we can
see that anyone can become
so
if you
consume
more, I can get it by
clicking, I am
sitting a little higher, I have done
exercise from college, Lumba works in the Railways,
when once the publicity came on
your skin, after such a president, we
infamously made Jasmine reversal, a little bit of
price festival, six morality and
Nifty background 136 56, some
time ago, Prithvi kept a lot of comments on his and gas, everyone
's body, moral spread, but
you covered that after the members of porn
and I think some time ago, see the
comments that were coming from ITC on i30,
that was tough in the meeting which I said, rough,
although TCS mentioned about both the hotel businesses
that the income has doubled
till now and we have
seen the price performance of ITC quite well
in the last month
and the way the cost completion of these adversity companies has become
quite loose
in the last one and a half months, you come at this time, let me tell
you  We can
add to your point
that we see this happening in some city specific stocks
where we can have
positive focus, if we
talk about pimples, there is not full staff, such jewelry is
very damaged and the utensils which
were not clean, you can write management, then from here we will
show with disgust, so that improvement
you have, my point is that last
month's rally, so this is subscribed for basic
and that on
one hand the
inventory of disgust
because companies have been deployed, so it is
also the case that if the press has increased today, then
more free clause will be deducted, so all good,
without doing anything like this, the numbers and the country wise
got it, now this
inventory which was launched, the
second thing always remember
and the
conjunction of Mohit is that it should not be temporary
but it will hit in the coming time, so it
means that if you are reading this post,
you have money to
spend,
I believe that this was so,
but we will talk, then
wait a little and when the problem of jobs question
starts, then after that we will
look for a move in this sector  We
'll start right now, for now, absolutely nothing.
Here, Yadav Usha Qualification Ajit.
Look at both the charts once. IT Chor Chor and
our Dal screen. You have seen the one-year
trend where you have seen a lakh Yahoo
lift with this crop returns
and Actual is showing a game of up to eight percent.
This was a matter of one year, but
if you look at the last one month,
Actual has seen more action.
Apart from this, it was seen playing catch-up with ITC
and in fact, it has gone ahead. The
question is that if someone is making a new investment on these labels, will the
ITC at 297 give a better return or the
Actual at 26. Ajit Chakli, tell me what you are
reading
and
look at this, the
quest is going to happen in the way we have
got photos time and without getting to see the fearless free
porn book display land, the
way in which the
queer
reason will go, so here you can go down
that is your record. By
reducing your subscription by ₹10  We can give you
rates of
interest in the short term. You
should have a dumbbell plan. If the straight line is
more attractive for you, then look at such a plan. There has been a
gain of up to 7.25 cm in the last 12
months. But if we want to
take a new trend from today's perspective, then actually we will have
shown unbearable returns of up to 40%. There is
actually negative news about cement companies.
Different companies are being
accused of account realization and
here the companies can be fined a lot.
More details. The protest is
with us. Alok told what they are catching.
Look, the
CBI investigation against these cement companies
started three years ago, its scope has
now increased from six companies to 20 companies.
CNBC Awaaz has
received information from sources that the
investigation of the Competition Commission has been completed
and all the 20 companies including
Ultratech, Dalmia, Shree Cement, Babua,
Vista and Ambuja Cement are all these
companies.  The
CCI has
given a one-month notice to the wedding music companies to present their side.
After receiving their response within one month, the
BCCI will decide the penalty amount.
We are getting information
that the amount could be 10 percent of the turnover
or three times the profit. Along with this, there is a
preparation to impose such a huge fine, provided that if the
response of the companies given
by the CBI is not satisfactory, it is said that
overall, the
investigation was going on regarding the reason for this cartelization.
In the investigation
[music], the
companies have contacted TRAI
and through email, all the companies which are
computer companies in it, were in touch with each other and there was
anticipation and
despite there being competition, they used to
decide the prices among themselves. Especially in this
way, this has been seen to be very Ramchand in great returns. So,
all these investigations have been done.
Based on the investigation, the companies have been asked to respond.
After receiving the response, the
amount of the huge penalty will be decided and an order will be
issued for it,
which is called one.  Bitter gourd covered with neem
means that it is innocent and looks bad from the outside, the
cost percentage during this period
was 5 kg boiled and this license which is said
that war happens after a year, something
definitely comes and abstracts the companies,
now I heard from you and your
first example here is aware of these
companies, what is our, this is not the first time this has happened,
this has happened many times in history,
yes you are absolutely right that this will be
given by CCI many times before, Jai Kishan, but secondly make it difficult
that something like this has happened, you can try to click on
subscribe,
I think you should
not subscribe and now the
school is going through trouble because the time is
very much, so whatever will start happening,
please
subscribe to it, so for
some time
we
need it there and as much as I will bring deep in the negative water, then I will bring a
lot of tomatoes, just duty, if we
suppress 2357 then it is very good, but right now
because we know that the next two quarters will be
bad then we will wait, at this time
we will do cement through real estate,
so at any time MS Word is better,
we will have very good there  Options are available and
all this interest is there, please like cement will have
problem, it is important to find the same benefit for real estate,
so there the person can mix this money for
cement money in real estate,
develop Maharana Press you
are one and Brigade Enterprises Papaya
Bill dust hindrance and remember that in view of this news
some shopping will come out
because these charts are such that these price
portions are such that till now they have not even participated in this journey of the market
from 15200 to
around 16500 087